## **BOGDAN MIHOCI**

IUNIOR FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

0745 4440 442



bogdanmihoci27@gmail.com



IP12 1JL, Woodbridge



LinkedIn

### EDUCATION

**COMPUTING & IT** 

BSc, Open University

June 2014 – June 2020

#### TECHNOLOGIES

Java

JavaScript

React, Redux

HTML/ CSS

SQL, My-SQL, MongoDB

Junit, Mockito

Swing, JavaFX

Visual Studio Code

IntelliJ, Eclipse, NetBeans

Maven, Gradle

Git

Liquibase

Swagger

#### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a Junior Full Stack Developer with basic experience in designing, documenting, testing and implementing new, custom applications for commercial use. In my work, I continually strive to seamlessly blend the demands of modern business with the world of technology. As an enthusiastic, passionate and motivated person, I am keen to analyse complex requirements and developing an in-depth understanding of the company's needs and objectives, creating solutions to add value to all company operations through increased efficiency. I pride myself in my ability to build user-friendly interfaces and continuously optimize the code for faster performance. My goal-oriented mindset, prompt troubleshooting and problem-solving skills help me ensure the timely completion of all my projects.

My work at GitHub.

#### MAIN PROJECTS

#### PURCHASE REQUEST SYSTEM

**Hatcher Components** 

- App allowing anyone within the business to search through a lengthy catalog of products, complete internal purchase requests and save, print or email orders directly to the company buyer. Offering traceability, transparency and access from different company sites.
- This application fully replaced the previous company-wide manual purchasing system
- Technology: Java, My-SQL, Swing

#### NON-CONFORMANCE MANAGEMENT SYSTEM

**Hatcher Components** 

- App streamlining the complaint process, from client rejection through investigation, root cause analyses all the way to resolution
- Custom system designed for logging in all details of internal, supplier and customer non-conformances, implementing corrective actions allowing efficient case monitoring and providing a data analyses tool
- Technology: Java, My-SQL, Swing

#### **ENGINEERING CHANGES SYSTEM**

Hatcher Components

- App enabling users to submit change request to company systems, products and services, which get reviewed weekly by a committee to allow organic continuous process improvement on-site
- The app provided the team with reliable way to assign, monitor, set deadlines and log engineering changes across all company factories.
- Technology: Java, My-SQL, Swing

#### COURSES

#### **REACT**

The Complete Guide (Hooks, React Router, Redux)

Udemy

### SPRING & HIBERNATE FOR BEGINNERS

(Spring Boot)
Udemy

### THE COMPLETE JAVASCRIPT COURSE

2019 Edition

Udemy

### JAVA SPRING TUTORIAL MASTER CLASS

Learn Spring Framework
Udemy

### MASTERING MICROSERVICES WITH JAVA

LinkedIn Learning

#### SPRING:

Test-Driven Development with JUnit LinkedIn Learning

#### SPRING:

Spring Cloud

LinkedIn Learning

#### LEARNING DOCKER

LinkedIn Learning

#### JHIPSTER:

Build and Deploy Spring Boot Microservices

LinkedIn Learning

#### GIT:

Branches, Merges, and Remotes
LinkedIn Learning

# EXTENDING, SECURING AND DOCKERIZING SPRING BOOT

MICROSERVICES
LinkedIn Learning

#### EXPERIENCE

#### PRODUCTION MANAGER ASSISTANT

Hatcher Components / November 2013 - Present

- Developed various bespoke software solutions for Hatcher Components
- Collaborated on the Manual Manufacturing to a PLC Factory Automation System Upgrade project
- Programmed an automated production system in under 5 weeks using Ladder Logic language
- Created instructions and guidelines for assembly and fitting processes
- Coordinated the assembly work, ensuring high product quality
- Planned materials to support workshop production

#### FOREMAN

Hatcher Components / April 2012 – November 2013

- Managed a team in the Finishing and Assembly Department
- Supervised, coordinated, and scheduled on-site activities, assisted workers and arranged for maintenance and machinery repairs

#### **ASSEMBLER**

Hatcher Components / February 2011 - April 2012

 Interpreted schematic diagrams and engineering specifications, and conducted quality checks on finished products

#### CORPORAL (LOGISTICS DIVISION)

Romanian Army / January 2008 - February 2011

Received basic military, survival, first aid and fitness training

#### LANGUAGES

ENGLISH: Fluent

ROMANIAN: Native

#### OTHER TECHNOLOGIES INCLUDE

AWS RESTful Web Services JHipster

Hibernate Postman Microservices

Spring Framework JWT Authentication Netflix Eureka

Spring MVC Oauth2 Authentication Hystrix

Spring Boot Docker Compose